premiumapplicationsdownloads.com 2014-02-22

# Site Privacy Policy

##  Site Privacy Policy 

** Do we use cookies? **

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information 

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.. ** Do we disclose any information to outside parties? **

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

** Third party links **

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

** Unsolicited email messages **

We prohibit any advertising of our PREMIUMAPPLICATIONSDOWNLOADS.COM web site using unsolicited email messages. Not complying with this policy will cause partnership termination and/or affiliate account termination.   
If you feel you've been sent unsolicited emails promoting our brand or website and would like to register a complaint, please contact us at <http://premiumapplicationsdownloads.com/contactus>. We will immediately investigate all allegations made related to unsolicited messages. 

** Your Consent **

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy 

. ** Changes to our Privacy Policy **

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on October 1, 2012
